<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Aila Baron</title>
    <link>https://ailabaron.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Aila Baron</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Aila Baron</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://ailabaron.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeopathy</title>
      <link>https://ailabaron.github.io/homeopathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ailabaron.github.io/homeopathy/</guid>
      
        <description>What is Homeopathy? Homeopathy is over 200 years old and is practised both by doctors and Homeopaths across the world. According to statistics over 200 million people worldwide use Homeopathy. It is part of the National Health Service in several countries, including Switzerland and India and to a lesser degree the UK. In the UK there are 1500 Homeopaths and 500 Homeopathic doctors. Homeopathy is a natural therapy where homeopathic medicines/remedies are prescribed.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started</title>
      <link>https://ailabaron.github.io/get-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ailabaron.github.io/get-started/</guid>
      
        <description>If you have had a problem for a while and it has become chronic you can come and see me for, what we call, Constitutional treatment. This is where you require the skills of a professional Homeopath to find that unique remedy that works for you on both physical and emotional levels. Allow a minimum of two hours for the first consultation (less for children) which is conducted in a friendly, relaxed athmosphere.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ailabaron.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ailabaron.github.io/contact/</guid>
      
        <description>Aila Baron, RSHom
You can reach me directly via
email : baronshouse2000(at)yahoo(dot)com
phone : 0208 888 6536
My practices are at:
 Alexandra Park, North London
phone: 0208 888 6536
  on Wednesdays:
Natural Health
4 Old Cross, Hertford
Hertfordshire SG14 1RB
phone: 01992 55 01 01
www.naturaltherapycentre.co.uk
 I am also available for consultations over Zoom or Skype.
You can also use the contact form below. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to hearing from you.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
