<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Aila Baron</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Aila Baron</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Aila Baron</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeopathy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/homeopathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/homeopathy/</guid>
      
        <description>What Is Homeopathy? Homeopathy is a natural therapy that uses homeopathic remedies/medicines. Its story started over two hundred years ago when a German doctor/chemist Samuel Hahneman wanted to find a more gentle way of healing than the brutal treatments of his day. Today’s patients are also drawn to homeopathy because of its natural, gentle nature. When you visit a homeopath you will see that they give you a lot of time and space to express your health issues, emotions or whatever brings you to them.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/get-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/get-started/</guid>
      
        <description>If you have not yet taken the decision to see a homeopath, maybe you can start to use homeopathic remedies for some simple acute conditions. This ,for a lot of people is their first introduction to the world of Homeopathy.
Most people will have heard of Arnica , the most famous homeopathic remedy for injuries and bruising. Many surgeons now tell their patients to take Arnica after surgery Here is a list of some common remedies to use in acute situations:</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      
        <description>My name is Aila Baron, RSHom
You can reach me directly via
email : baronshouse2000(at)yahoo(dot)com
phone : 0208 888 6536
My practices are at
Natural Health Hertford &amp;mdash; wednesdays
01992 589 439
in North London, N22 &amp;mdash; rest of the week
0208 888 6536
You can also youse the contact form below. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to hearing from you.
Wird geladen… </description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
